My life lesson is that resiliency pays off.
My mother’s dreams for me was to live an
easier life than hers.
She did not want me to struggle and fight
as much as she did.
That’s why she always reminded me to keep
my education first.
By December of my first semester of university,
my mom had passed away from cancer.
If my mother had had life insurance, things
would have been a lot easier for both me and
my siblings.
I would have been able to go to school without
thinking of money so much and funeral costs
would have been paid for.
When I found the Manulife Life Lessons Scholarship,
I was in shock.
I thought this is exactly my life and I did
not understand or realize that there were
other people who went through what I went
through.
It felt like someone wanted to hear my story
for the first time.
The process of applying to the Manulife Life
Lessons Scholarship was easy.
The difficult part was thinking about all
the life lessons I’ve had to learn thus
far.
Before I had this scholarship, I was working
3 jobs and had 16-hour long days with school
and work.
Since I got the scholarship, I’ve been able
to focus more on school, I haven’t had to
work as much, and I’ve been able to get
involved in the community a lot more.
My life lesson is resiliency pays off because
there were many times I wanted to quit and
give up but it was resiliency that kept me
motivated.
I am very much my mother’s daughter.
She never gave up and neither will I.
To someone thinking of applying to the Manulife
Life Lessons Scholarship, my advice is to
just do it.
It will change your life as much as it’s
changed mine.